<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Keesing McLeod</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Keesing McLeod</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Post 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-3/</guid>
      <description>Occaecat aliqua consequat laborum ut ex aute aliqua culpa quis irure esse magna dolore quis. Proident fugiat labore eu laboris officia Lorem enim. Ipsum occaecat cillum ut tempor id sint aliqua incididunt nisi incididunt reprehenderit. Voluptate ad minim sint est aute aliquip esse occaecat tempor officia qui sunt. Aute ex ipsum id ut in est velit est laborum incididunt. Aliqua qui id do esse sunt eiusmod id deserunt eu nostrud aute sit ipsum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-2/</guid>
      <description>Anim eiusmod irure incididunt sint cupidatat. Incididunt irure irure irure nisi ipsum do ut quis fugiat consectetur proident cupidatat incididunt cillum. Dolore voluptate occaecat qui mollit laborum ullamco et. Ipsum laboris officia anim laboris culpa eiusmod ex magna ex cupidatat anim ipsum aute. Mollit aliquip occaecat qui sunt velit ut cupidatat reprehenderit enim sunt laborum. Velit veniam in officia nulla adipisicing ut duis officia.&#xA;Exercitation voluptate irure in irure tempor mollit Lorem nostrud ad officia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Tempor proident minim aliquip reprehenderit dolor et ad anim Lorem duis sint eiusmod. Labore ut ea duis dolor. Incididunt consectetur proident qui occaecat incididunt do nisi Lorem. Tempor do laborum elit laboris excepteur eiusmod do. Eiusmod nisi excepteur ut amet pariatur adipisicing Lorem.&#xA;Occaecat nulla excepteur dolore excepteur duis eiusmod ullamco officia anim in voluptate ea occaecat officia. Cillum sint esse velit ea officia minim fugiat. Elit ea esse id aliquip pariatur cupidatat id duis minim incididunt ea ea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACC</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/acc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/acc/</guid>
      <description>One of the fascinating aspects of practising law in a relatively small centre such as Lower Hutt is that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take long before the economic ramifications of any governmental or administrative policy decisions or changes become known to you through the increased number of clients sitting in your waiting room. From my perspective this certainly appears the case with what seems to be an unannounced but very definite push to get as many people off earnings related and other compensation under the Accident Insurance Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are We Now Moving Towards Joint Custody of Children Following Separation?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/are-we-now-moving-towards-joint-custody-of-children-following-separation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/are-we-now-moving-towards-joint-custody-of-children-following-separation/</guid>
      <description>When couples separate, particularly when they separate acrimoniously, fights over property can be stressful and hurtful. It is however the disputes over the care of children that cause the greatest anguish. Where the care of children cannot be resolved by counselling or mediation and proceed to Court for a Judge to make a determination then it is likely that the outcome will result in one parent being happier than the other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ben Davie</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-law-firm/ben-davie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-law-firm/ben-davie/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business Sales and Acquisitions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/our-services/business-sales-and-acquisitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/our-services/business-sales-and-acquisitions/</guid>
      <description>Our team excels in facilitating the purchase and sale of businesses across various industries. We provide comprehensive support, from thorough due diligence to strategic contract negotiations, ensuring a smooth transition and successful closure. Whether acquiring a new business or divesting an existing one, we safeguard your interests and maximise your investment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buying a house - Traps for the unwary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/buying-a-house-traps-for-the-unwary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/buying-a-house-traps-for-the-unwary/</guid>
      <description>When putting in an offer for a house it is most advisable to either have a lawyer check the Agreement before you sign it or to make it subject to your lawyer&amp;rsquo;s approval. Because, in practice, many people sign contracts to purchase homes before they consult a lawyer, here are some of the traps for the unwary:&#xA;Deposits&#xA;There is no legal requirement as to the amount of a deposit. Certainly it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t exceed 10% and is often less.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Care Of Children Act 2004</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/care-of-children-act-2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/care-of-children-act-2004/</guid>
      <description>On 1 July 2005 the first major change in 37 years to the law relating to the care of children came into force. The Guardianship Act 1968 was replaced by the Care of Children Act 2004. Cynics were quick to point out that the most obvious difference is that the law relating to children had expanded from about 60 sections to 164 sections. It is true that many of the changes consist of saying the same thing in longer sentences, but there are also some major changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commercial and Industrial Leasing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/our-services/commercial-and-industrial-leasing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/our-services/commercial-and-industrial-leasing/</guid>
      <description>Keesing McLeod specialises in leasing commercial and industrial properties. We negotiate favourable terms, draft and review lease agreements, and resolve disputes proactively. Our team also provides detailed advice on lease obligations and rights, ensuring you are well-informed and protected throughout the leasing process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Guarantees Act</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/consumer-guarantees-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/consumer-guarantees-act/</guid>
      <description>As Christmas is upon us I thought I would write about a topic appropriate to the season of excessive consumer expenditure.&#xA;It is not an uncommon experience to purchase an item and then regret the purchase soon after coming home. Sometimes that regret sets in, in respect of clothing items, when a less than enthusiastic response is received to the anxious query “Does it suit me?” Can you then immediately return that item and get your money back?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate and Commercial Law</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/our-services/corporate-and-commercial-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/our-services/corporate-and-commercial-law/</guid>
      <description>We provide bespoke legal advice on corporate structuring, compliance, and intellectual property. Our strategic guidance through contracts, mergers, and acquisitions helps safeguard your assets and propel your business forward. Navigate the complexities of commercial law with our expert support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you need a Family Trust?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/do-you-need-a-family-trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/do-you-need-a-family-trust/</guid>
      <description>Family Trusts may be created for a whole variety of reasons. Primarily however, in recent times, they have been created for the purposes of protection of assets. Trusts can provide protection for personal assets in the following cases:&#xA;Protection of assets from creditors. Protection of assets in the case of marital or relationship break ups. Protection of assets against claims to property after death. Protection of assets in relation to costs of aged care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Battah</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-law-firm/don-battah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-law-firm/don-battah/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employment Law</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/our-services/employment-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/our-services/employment-law/</guid>
      <description>Keesing McLeod offers comprehensive legal guidance in employment law. We draft individual employment agreements, advise on workplace policies, and work effectively and practically to resolve disputes. We act for either employers or employees in resolving employment issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employment Law Basics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/employment-law-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/employment-law-basics/</guid>
      <description>I am still surprised at the lack of knowledge of the basic requirements of employment law shown by many employers and employees that I come in contact with. It might be useful to look at two matters over which there is much misunderstanding.&#xA;The first is that everyone in New Zealand who is employed must have an employment agreement. They either have their own individual employment agreement or, if part of a union, they are covered by a union collective agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employment Relations Act</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/employment-relations-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/employment-relations-act/</guid>
      <description>The Employment Relations Act is coming up for its first year anniversary. This time last year you couldn&amp;rsquo;t pick up a paper without reading widely diverging views as to how this legislation would change the face of New Zealand society. Now what do you read - nothing! What&amp;rsquo;s the story here, was Ms Wilson right in predicting that the new legislation would seamlessly integrate itself into our employment culture? Well, sort of.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estate Administration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/our-services/estate-administration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/our-services/estate-administration/</guid>
      <description>Managing the distribution of a deceased person’s estate is a profound responsibility. We provide meticulous estate administration services, ensuring each estate is settled according to the deceased wishes and legal requirements. Trust us to handle your estate administration with care and dignity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Law</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/our-services/family-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/our-services/family-law/</guid>
      <description>Our approach to family law is pragmatic and focused on achieving the most favorable outcomes for our clients. We handle separation, relationship property, custody negotiations, and prenuptial agreements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If we separate we will just divide everything in half, we don&#39;t need a lawyer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/if-we-separate-we-will-just-divide-everything-in-half-we-dont-need-a-lawyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/if-we-separate-we-will-just-divide-everything-in-half-we-dont-need-a-lawyer/</guid>
      <description>I am (sadly) old enough to have been practising law when the Matrimonial Property Act 1976 came into force and effect. It was a revolutionary piece of legislation. Before then a party to a marriage had to prove their contribution to an asset before they could take a share of it on separation. So a wife and mother might devote 40 years of her life to bringing up 6 children, managing the farm accounts, work from dawn to dusk on the farm alongside her husband, and find at the end of the day she had a very limited claim to the farm when the marriage came to an end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration Law</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/our-services/immigration-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/our-services/immigration-law/</guid>
      <description>Navigate New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s immigration landscape with our expert legal assistance. We specialise in:&#xA;Visa applications Citizenship procedures Family sponsorship Entrepreneur and investor visas Handling appeals, We simplify the immigration process, ensuring full compliance with legal requirements and helping you achieve your goals with clarity and confidence. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamie Steele</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-law-firm/jamie-steele/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-law-firm/jamie-steele/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Comerford</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-law-firm/john-comerford/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-law-firm/john-comerford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter McLeod</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-law-firm/peter-mcleod/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-law-firm/peter-mcleod/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Property Sales and Acquisitions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/our-services/property-sales-and-acquisitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/our-services/property-sales-and-acquisitions/</guid>
      <description>At Keesing McLeod, we expertly guide you through buying, selling, and transferring property ownership. Whether you are a first-time homebuyer, a seasoned investor, or a business expanding its footprint, we ensure that every transaction aligns with your strategic goals. Our comprehensive services include contract management, strategic negotiation, and thorough due diligence, all aimed at a smooth and efficient transaction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporary Employment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/temporary-employment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/temporary-employment/</guid>
      <description>We are at that merry time of year when young people&amp;rsquo;s thoughts turn to trying to get some employment over the Christmas holiday period to fund the ever increasing costs of tertiary education. Others are looking to increase family revenues with additional employment. Happily it is also the time of year when many businesses require extra help. Unfortunately however employers may be reluctant to hire part time casual or seasonal staff due to worries about the cost of compliance with the new Employment Relations Act and employment relationship difficulties that might ensue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Implications of Property Ownership</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/the-implications-of-property-ownership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/the-implications-of-property-ownership/</guid>
      <description>The enjoyment, control, protection and bequeathing of personal assets and investments are all affected by the manner in which those assets are owned.&#xA;Ownership can be classified into a number of different categories.&#xA;Individual Personal Owndership&#xA;The advantages of individual personal ownership include full control and enjoyment; no obligations or responsibilities to others; disposable by Will; and no extra costs.&#xA;The disadvantages are that the property may be available to creditors on bankruptcy; may be included in asset testing; may have tax disadvantages; may be challenged if disposed of by Will; and may be viewed as “relationship property” under the revamped Property (Relationships) Act 1976 which comes into force 1 February 2002.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Needs to be in an Employment Agreement?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/what-needs-to-be-in-an-employment-agreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/what-needs-to-be-in-an-employment-agreement/</guid>
      <description>One of the most common requests I get is to look at an individual employment agreement to make sure its alright. An advantage of my practice is that I act for both employers and employees. That means I can assist employers in drafting up agreements as well as advising employee clients as to whether the agreement they present me with is fair or not.&#xA;I thought it might be useful to set out the important things that should be in anyone&amp;rsquo;s employment agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wills, Family Trusts, Asset Protection, and Succession Planning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/our-services/wills-and-estate-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/our-services/wills-and-estate-planning/</guid>
      <description>Secure your future with our expert estate planning services. We draft precise wills, establish robust family trusts, and formulate asset protection strategies. Our collaborative approach ensures your personal and business succession plans reflect your wishes and provide peace of mind.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
